What's going on?
ماذا يجري؟
Why are you here?!
!لماذا أنت هنا؟
How did you get on board?!
!كيف ركبت؟
What in the world...?
!كيف؟
How do you do?
سررت للقائك
I'm Sogeking, King of Snipers.
أنا ملك القناصين، سوغيكينغ
To make a long story short, I've come to rescue you.
اختصارًا للحديث، أتيت لإنقاذك
Long Nose...
طويل الأنف-كن
It's not just me.
ليس أنا فحسب
Sir Sanji and a thug named Franky are currently engaged in battle on this train.
سانجي-كن وبلطجي يدعى فرانكي يتقاتلان على متى هذا القطار الآن
It gave me a chance to come here.
وخلال قتاليهما، وجدت فرصة للقدوم إلى هنا
Also, Sir Luffy and the others
علاوة على ذلك، لوفي-كن والبقية
are pursuing us on this very railway aboard another sea train…
،يلاحقوننا في نفس الاتجاه لكن على متن قطار بحري مختلف
Apparently, they're bringing quite a few allies.
ومعهم حلفاء أيضًا
On my way here, I peeked inside through the windows.
،في طريقي إلى هنا قبل قليل استرقت النظر إلى داخل القطار عبر النوافذ
Frankly, the team of four in the car behind us is dangerous.
بصراحة، الأشخاص الأربعة الموجودين في المقطورة الخلفية خطيرون
It'd be best if I could get you out of here before Sir Sanji confronts them.
سيكون من الأفضل لو تمكنت من إنقاذك قبل أن يواجههم سانجي-كن
Now, let us escape...
هيّا، لنهرب
together!
!معًا
What's the matter?
ما الخطب؟
There's no need to worry.
لا داعي للقلق
I'm all prepared.
أنا مستعد جيّدًا
These octoshoes are for you.
هذه أحذية أخطبوط من أجلك
Wear these on your hands and feet
،إن ارتديتها في يديك ورجليك
so that we can climb out the window and cling to the sea train.
فستتمكنين من الخروج عبر النافذة والالتصاق بألواح القطار البحري الخارجية
Now, put them on before they notice.
هيّا، ارتديها قبل أن يلاحظوا
Wait.
انتظر
"Wait"?
انتظر؟
How could this be happening?
لماذا يحدث هذا؟
I thought I clearly told you all goodbye.
يفترض أنّي ودعتكم بوضوح
I'll never return to the Straw Hats!
!لن أعود إلى الطاقم ثانية
They know why you are so insistent about that.
يعرفون سبب إصرارك على هذا
I heard that the Ice fellow at the shipyard clarified everything.
سمعت أنّ العم أيس في حوض السفانة وضّح كلّ شيء
So he survived?
إنّه بخير؟
No...
لا، بغض النظر
I won't return to you guys...
!لن أعود إليكم
Enough of that!
!كفاكِ ثرثرة
You still don't get it?!
!ألا تزالين لا تفهمين؟
They're not so weak that you need to worry about them!
!ليسوا ضعافًا لدرجة أنّك تحتاجين أن تقلقي عليهم
They really wish you would've spoken to them before taking such a stupid deal!
،قبل أن تقبلي صفقة غبية كهذه !أرادوا منك أن تتحدثي معهم أولًا
You really think they'd be happy to be alive
أتعتقدين أنّهم سيسعدون لنجاتهم
knowing their friend gave her life for theirs?!
بمعرفتهم أنّ ذلك كان !بسبب تضحية صديقتهم بنفسها؟
Now that they know why you left them,
،بما أنّهم عرفوا سبب هجرك لهم الآن
they'll follow you to the depths of hell and take down your enemies!
فسيتبعوك حتّى أعماق الجحيم !ويطيحوا بأعدائك
You still don't get what kind of man Luffy is!
!ما زلتِ لم تفهمي شخصية الرجل لوفي
It's you guys who don't get it!
!أنتم من لا يفهم
I don't have the slightest desire to be rescued!
!لا أمتلك أدنى رغبة بأن ينقذني أحد
You can't just do as you please!
!لا تفعلوا ما يحلو لكم
What'd you say, you–
...ماذا قلتِ أيّتها
What are you making a racket for, Nico Robin?
ما هذا الإزعاج يا نيكو روبين؟
What's the matter?
ما الخطب؟
Now that we're approaching Enies Lobby, is it hard for even you to remain calm?
،بما أنّنا اقتربنا من إنيس لوبي فهل بدأ الحفاظ على هدوئك يصبح صعبًا؟
Cry about your fate all you like.
،حتى لو بكيتِ على مصيرك الآن
It won't do anything to save your life.
!فلن يُنقذ ذلك حياتك
It's nothing.
لا شيء
What was that?
ما كان ذلك؟
Very suspicious...
!شيء غريب
Also, she seems different somehow…
علاوة على ذلك، تبدو مختلفة عن السابق
Is it just my imagination?
أيخيل لي ذلك؟
It's nothing...
لا شيء
so please leave me alone.
لذا اتركني وحدي
What the hell?
ما هذا؟
Why is this woman goofing around?
ما خطب هذه المرأة؟
A rabbit...?
أرنب؟
Welcome to the world of ramen kenpo!
!مرحبًا بك في عالم فن القتال بالرامن
What sort of power-up...?
ما الذي أصبح أقوى؟
Now, now, now!
!هيّا، هيّا، هيّا، خذ هذه
Ramen Kenpo:
فن القتال بالرامن
Pork Bone Spank!
صفعة عظم لحم الخنزير
Isn't that just a bigger version of the same worthless punch?
إنّها مجرد لكمة عقيمة مكبّرة
Now, now, now! Another one!
!هيّا، هيّا، هيّا! أخرى
I-I'm stuck!
!عـ-علقت
Now, now!
!هيّا، هيّا
Now, now, now!
!هيّا، هيّا، هيّا! أيّها الغبي
Are you taken aback by my ramen kenpo?!
!أتفاجأت بفن القتال بالرمان خاصتي؟
You look unsightly with your leg and arm buried in ramen noodles!
!تبدو بشعًا وساقك ويدك عالقة داخل الرامن
Who do you think you are, beating the snot outta me earlier?!
!كيف تجرؤ على برحي ضربًا قبل قليل؟
Are you seriously getting dizzy on me?!
!لماذا أُصبت بالدوار أيّها الوغد؟
You tried to make me woozy with your eyebrows again!
حاولتَ أن تُصيبني بالدوار !مرة ثانية باستخدام حاجبك، أليس كذلك؟
I'm not gonna let you get away with it!
!لن أغفر لك
Dammit!
!تبًا
I can't fight back like this!
!لا أستطيع سحب نفسي
Noodle Soul Press!
ضغط روح المعكرونة
I'm just getting started!
!لم أنتهِ بعد
Another helping!
!خذ هذه
And another!
!وهذه
Take that, and that, and that, and that, and that, and that, and that!
!خذ هذه وهذه وهذه وهذه وهذه وهذه وهذه
They finally came off.
فلتّ أخيرًا
Now, now, now!
!هيّا، هيّا، هيّا
Aren't you underestimating me, you dummy?
ألست تستخف بي أيّها الأحمق؟
This is the mad, mad ramen kenpo!
!هذا فن القتال بالرامن المجنون
If I attack, I get buried in ramen...
لم أعتقد أنّي سأعلق إن هاجمت الرامن
I guess I can't touch those noodles.
لا ينبغي لي لمس الرامن إذًا
Now, I'll keep it coming!
!هيّا، سأستمر
Ramen-Gyoza Combo:
خليط الرامن والغيوزا
Clapping!
صفق
So there's only one place I can aim for, huh?
إذًا، أستطيع مهاجمته في مكان واحد فقط
Éscalope!
الشرائح الرقيقة
Ramen Beam!
شعاع الرامن
Now, now, now!
!هيّا، هيّا، هيّا
I've got no blind spot!
!لا أملك نقطة عمياء
From what I've seen, your fighting style is made up of kicks, isn't it?
ممّا رأيته حتّى الآن، فإنّ أسلوبك بالقتال هو الركل، أليس كذلك؟
You're helpless without your kicks, aren't you?
لا تملك شيئًا سوى الركل، أليس كذلك؟
Now, now, now!
!هيّا، هيّا، هيّا! لا فائدة، لا فائدة
No matter what you do, you'll only end up being buried in my suit!
مهما فعلت، فسينتهي بك المطاف !عالقًا في بذلتي فحسب
Here goes! Try dodging this!
!هيّا! حاول تفاديها
Ramen Kenpo:
فن القتال بالرامن
Multi-Noodle Spank!
صفعات المعكرونة المتعددة
Fedelini: a 1.4 millimeter pasta...
فيدليني: نوع من أنواع المعكرونة الإيطالية
Sleight of hand...?
خفّة يد؟
You cut my noodle fists to pieces!
!قبضات الرامن خاصتي تقطّعت إلى أجزاء
Hands and kitchen knives are sacred to cooks.
اليدان وسكاكين المطبخ مقدسة بالنسبة للطباخين
So it's my policy not to use them in a battle.
ولذلك فإنّ سياستي هي عدم استخدامها في القتال
But if this is a kitchen...
ولكن إن كان هذا مطبخ
and my enemy is made of food, then it's a different story.
وعدوّي مكوّن طعام، فسيختلف الأمر
You're more troublesome than I thought.
إنّك مزعج أكثر مما توقعت
Thousand-Noodle Whip!
سوط الألف معكرونة
Trying to look cool?
!تحاول أن تبدو رائعًا؟! يا لك من متغطرس
An amateur like you who can't even cook shouldn't hold kitchen knives!
لا ينبغي لمبتدئ لا يستطيع حتّى !الطّبخ مثلك أن يحمل سكاكين المطبخ
They're different from the knives that delinquents use!
!إنّها تختلف عن التي يستخدمها الجانحون
Pardon me for being saucy.
اعذرني على كوني متغطرسًا
Accept this as a token of my apology.
،تقبّل هذا بمثابة اعتذار
Allow me to show you...
دعني أريك
how a first-class cook...
!كيف يتعامل طبّاخ الدرجة الأولى مع سكاكين المطبخ
Shave!
الركض الفائق
Strong Hammer!
المطرقة القوية
Paper Art.
فن الورق
Tempest Kick!
ركلة العاصفة
Fresh Fire!
النار المنعشة
Shave!
الركض الفائق
Wha...?! What's his deal?! He just went and jumped off the train!
!ماذا؟! ما خطبه؟ !قفز إلى البحر من تلقاء نفسه
Moon Walk!
مشية القمر
How'd he bounce back here in midair?!
!كيف ارتدّ في الهواء؟! لا أفهم ما يجري
Why can't I cut him with Tempest Kick?
!لماذا لا أستطيع قطعه بركلة العاصفة؟ !ثمّة أمر غريب في جسده
What...
...من
...the hell...
...تكون
...are you?!
!أيّها الوغد؟
Are we close to the Bashing Tom yet?!
!ألم نقترب من باشينغ توم بعد؟
That's "Puffing"!
!إنّه بافينغ
Hey, Luffy! Stay inside!
!أنت يا لوفي، ادخل
You just changed, but you're soaking wet again!
!غيّرت ملابسك توًّا، ولكنّك تبللت بالكامل
That's okay!
!لا بأس
I like it up here!
!أعجبني هذا المكان
Geez...
...يا إلهي
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط
Three-Hundred-Pound...
ثلاثمئة رطل
– ...Cannon!
المدفع
– Ahh! This is it! Laguna!
!انتهى أمرنا! إنّها لاغونا
This is no time for playing around!
!لا تلهوا أيّها الأوغاد
– We're bored.
نشعر بالضجر
Go polish your weapons or something, you idiots!
!لمّعوا أسلحتكم أو ما شابه أيّها الحمقى
Well, um...
حسنًا
I'll talk to those guys later, so...
...سأتحدّث معهم لاحقًا، لذا
Hey, guys!
!أنتم
I see a train up ahead!
!أرى قطارًا أمامنا
– That's gotta be the Puffing Tom!
!لا بدّ أنّه بافينغ توم
Isn't it too early?
أليس هذا مبكرًا جدًّا؟
Dammit...
!سحقًا
What's gonna happen to us?
ماذا سيحدث لنا؟
There's no engine on this car. All we can do is wait for rescue.
لا يوجد محرّك في هذه المقطورة لا نملك خيارًا سوى انتظار إنقاذنا
Whoa! We're rocking!
!إنّنا نهتز
But what are the odds of rescue in a storm like this?
ولكن أسيأتي أحد لإنقاذنا في هذه العاصفة حقًا؟
Hey, guys. There's something coming from behind!
!يا جماعة، ثمّة شيء قادم من الخلف
Really?!
!حقًا؟
It must be a rescue ship!
!لا بدّ أنّها سفينة إنقاذ
Well, it looks like...
...لا، في الحقيقة
it's coming along the tracks.
!إنها تسير في مسارنا ذاته
Can't be...
...مستحيل
There's only one sea train in the world.
لا يوجد إلّا قطار بحري واحد في العالم
Besides, nothing could've left Water Seven after that last departure.
وأيضًا، رحلتنا من ووتر سيفن كانت الأخيرة
Then...
...إذًا
what the heck is coming?
ما القادم؟
Hey, that's a sea train, but it's just cars without the locomotive!
،استمعوا، إنّه قطار بحري !ولكن دون غرفة محرّك! مجرّد مقطورات
It's blocking the track!
!إنّها متوقفة على السكّة بلا حراك
What?!
!ماذا؟
What's going on?!
!ماذا يجري؟
Does this mean that they got detached?
أيعني ذلك أنّها فُصلت؟
Oh! Sanji and Usopp might be on them!
!ربّما سانجي وأوسوب داخلها
– Big Bro Franky, too!
!وأخي فرانكي أيضًا
This isn't good!
!هذا سيّئ
At this rate, we'll crash for sure!
!سنصطدم بهم إن استمررنا بالتقدّم هكذا
Lady! Where's the brake?!
!أيّتها الجدّة، أين المكابح؟
I said it doesn't work, didn't I?
ألم أخبركم أنّها لا تعمل؟
You'll have to do something.
تدبروا أمركم
We're gonna crash!
!سنصطدم
Luffy! What're you gonna do?
!لوفي! ماذا ستفعل؟
I'll go check inside!
!سأتحقّق من الداخل
Gum-Gum Rocket!
فاكهة المطاط: الصّاروخ
Something's flying...
طار شيء ما
What was that?
!ما ذلك؟
What is it?
ما هو؟
What happened?!
!ماذا حدث؟
Ow, ow, ow...
مؤلم، مؤلم، مؤلم
Alright! I got in!
!حسنًا، وصلت
Wh-Who are you?!
!مـ-من تكون؟
Hello! Sanji! Are you in here?!
!يا سانجي !هل أنت هنا؟
Usopp...
...أوسوب
Hello! Sanji! Hello!
!يا سانجي
Maybe over there?
ربما يكون هناك
This guy... Could it be...!
!هذا لا يمكن
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
!إنّه قبعة القش لوفي
Hello!
!أنت
Are you here, Sanji?!
!هل أنت هنا يا سانجي؟
Sanji!
!سانجي
Hey, shut up!
!اصمتوا
S-Straw Hat!
!قبعة القش
There's no escape for you!
!لن تستطيع الهرب
Where's Sanji?
أين سانجي؟
Wh-Who's that?
مـ-من هذا؟
Sanji! He's my friend!
!سانجي! إنّه رفيقي
We don't know a guy like that!
!لا نعرف شخصًا بهذا الاسم
I see...
فهمت
Then, see ya.
إلى اللقاء إذًا
Shoot him!
!أطلقوا
Straw Hat is coming out!
!خرج قبعة القش
He's saying that they're not in there... while being shot!
!يقول أنّ لا أحد هناك أثناء إطلاقهم النار عليه
Then, everyone in there is government personnel, huh?
إذًا جميع من في الداخل هم أتباع الحكومة؟
So what're you gonna do if so?
وماذا ستفعلون إذًا؟
If we don't move those cars, we'll take a lot of damage, too!
،ما لم نزحها عن طريقنا !فسنتلقى ضررًا كبيرًا أيضًا
That's a sea train, all right!
!إنّه قطار بحري فعلًا
We'll get knocked off!
!سيرتطمون بنا
Worse, we could all go up in a huge explosion!
!والأسوأ، قد نُهلك جميعًا في انفجار هائل
Stop!
!توقفوا
It's the Franky Family's time to shine.
حان دور عائلة فرانكي
We'll demolish them right before we crash!
!سندمرهم قبل اصطدامنا بهم مباشرة
Alright! We'll give you guys a hand, too!
!حسنًا، سنساعدكم أيضًا
Guys! It's time to work!
!حان وقت العمل يا جماعة
– Yeah!
!أجل
Hey! Zoro!
!يا زورو
Hey, Roronoa. He's calling your name.
إنّه يناديك يا رورونوا
Cut them. They're in our way.
اقطعهم، إنّهم يعيقون طريقنا
Sure.
حسنًا
– "Sure"?!
!حسنًا؟
The ego of the entropic world...
...يمكن لكبرياء العالم الانتروبيّ
can be slashed into pieces.
!أن تُقطّع إلى أجزاء
Two-Sword Style Draw...
سحب أسلوب السّيفين
Rashomon!
راشومون
– What?!
!ماذا؟
Hey, you guys!
أنتما
You could've told us you were gonna do that.
،إن كنتما ستفعلان شيئًا كهذا فينبغي لكما أن تخبرانا على الأقل
You heard me saying, "Cut them," right?!
!ألم تسمعني أقول له "اقطعهم"؟
We didn't think he actually could!
!يستحيل أن أظن أنّه يستطيع ذلك
We would've crashed if he didn't cut them, right?!
!كنّا سنصطدم ما لم يقطعهم، أليس كذلك؟
I guess that's true, but a little heads up would've been nice!
!هذا صحيح، ولكن كنا سنُهيئ أنفسنا
You're telling me a monster like him isn't even the captain?
حتّى وحش مثله ليس زعيم المجموعة؟
It's not over yet.
لم ننتهِ بعد
What the hell is that?!
!ما ذلك؟
It's a sea king!
!إنّه ملك بحر
Further ahead on this railway...
...أمامنا في هذه السكّة
lies the one who cut that thing up!
!الشخص الذي قطع هذا الشيء
Everyone, return to the front cars! It's a trap!
!عودوا إلى المقطورات الأماميّة جميعًا! هذا فخ
– A trap?!
!فخ؟
What the...?!
!ما هذا؟
To think that I fell for the enemy's scheme...
...بأن ينطلي مخطّط العدو عليّ
What a blunder!
!تخبّط
The gravest blunder of my life!
!هذا أكبر تخبّط في حياتي
Well then, gentlemen! Have a nice trip!
!حسنًا إذًا جميعًا، احظوا برحلة هانئة
I have to catch up with the sea train!
!عليّ لحاق القطار البحري
If the criminals we're supposed to escort are set free upon the world again...
...إن تحرّر المجرمون الذين يفترض بنا حراستهم ثانيةً
how much blood and how many tears will civilians have to shed?!
فكم من دماء المدنيين ستراق !وكم من دموعهم ستُذرف؟
I'll show them that there's justice even in this unfair world!
!سأثبت لهم وجود العدالة حتّى في هذا العالم الظالم
Even if my arms and legs are torn off by these raging waves...
حتّى وإن انقطعت قدماي ورجلاي ...من قبل هذه الأمواج العاتية
I will be sure to protect the future of innocent citizens!
!فسأنجو حتمًا لإنقاذ مستقبل المواطنين الأبرياء
What is that?
ما هذا؟
A sea train?
قطار بحري؟
Is that a new sea train?
أهذا قطار بحري جديد؟
There's something there!
!ثمّة شيء هناك
Huh? What's that?!
!ما هذا؟
A person? There's someone there!
!شخص؟ !يوجد شخص هناك
That's the Ship Slasher!
!إنّه قاطع السفن
– What?!
!ماذا؟
– S-Seriously?!
!حـ-حقًا؟
The Ship Slasher?
قاطع السفن؟
He's Ship Slasher T-Bone, a captain at Marine Headquarters!
!هذا قاطع السفن تي بون، عقيد في مقر البحريّة
He cuts pirate ships up like steaks!
!إنّه يقطع السفن كقِطع اللحم
Oh, yeah?
حقًا؟
That's amazing!
!مذهل
"Amazing"?! You're talking like it's someone else's problem!
!مذهل؟ !تتحدّث وكأنّ الأمر لا يعنيك
We can't just sit around like this.
لا يمكننا البقاء ساكنين هكذا
Hey, guys! Get ready to fire!
!يا رجال! استعدوا للإطلاق
Hurry up!
!أسرعوا
– Yeah!
!حسنًا
Wait!
!انتظروا
What is it?!
!ما الأمر؟
We'd better hurry up or he'll slash Rocketman!
!علينا أن نسرع وإلّا سيقطع روكيت مان
Weren't you watching earlier?
ماذا كنت تشاهد إلى الآن؟
Leave it to Zoro.
دعوا أمره لزورو
Don't interfere!
!لا تتدخّلوا
I'll tell you only once!
!لن أكرّر كلامي
Get out of our way!
!أفسح الطريق
My subordinates' cars were on the same railway, so they couldn't have simply passed them by.
لا يمكن أنّهم اجتازوا ببساطة مقطورات أتباعي التي كانت على نفس السكّة
What did these people do to my men?
ماذا فعلوا بأتباعي؟
They must be Nico Robin's crewmates...
لا بد أنّهم رفاق نيكو روبين
which means that swordsman is the Pirate Hunter!
!ما يعني أنّ ذلك السيّاف هو صائد القراصنة
This path leads to the seat of justice!
!يقود هذا المكان إلى منشأ العدالة
I'm a captain from Marine Headquarters!
!أنا عقيد في مقرّ البحريّة
I will not live in disgrace!
!لن أعيش في خزي
I'll stop you fiends by slashing you in two!
!سأوقفكم بقطعكم إلى نصفين
I can't allow that...
لن أسمح بذلك
as our destination lies beyond where you stand!
المكان الذي نبتغيه !يقع وراء مكان وقوفك
This guy is strong!
!إنّه قوي
Bring it on!
!واجهني
I detest crooked swordplay!
!أكره هجمات السيف الملتوية
Right-Angle Flying Bird:
طائر الزّاوية اليمنى المحلّق
Three-Sword Style:
أسلوب السّيوف الثّلاثة
Bull Demon!
الغول الثّور
Bone...
عظام العنقاء
He saw through it?!
!تنبأ بحركتي؟
Courageous Talons!
المخالب الجريئة
He beat the Ship Slasher!
!هزم قاطع السفن
To think that he followed the sea train from the detached cars in this storm...
لحق القطار البحري من المقطورات المفصولة في هذه العاصفة
How admirable!
!هذا جدير بالاحترام
But we can't stop here.
ولكن لا يمكننا أن نتوقف
I'm sure the burden of your justice is heavy, but we also shoulder our own burden.
،لا بدّ أنّ عدالتك عميقة أيضًا !ولكنّنا نحمل على عاتقنا أمور عديدة كذلك
Hurry! Hurry!
!أسرعوا! أسرعوا
Captain T-Bone jumped out to sea! He's in danger!
!العقيد تي بون الذي قفز في البحر يواجه الخطر
He could've been hit by that sea train by now.
!ربّما اصطدم به القطار البحري الآن
Watch your tongue, Marine!
!أيّها الوغد! لا تقل أمورًا كهذه
You should know that our captain would slash that train in two!
!سيقطع عقيدنا قطار بحري كذاك بسهولة
I-Is that right?
حـ-حقًا؟
That's right! I'm sure it's Sanji and the others who detached that sea train.
نعم، لا بدّ أنّ سانجي-كن والبقية هم من فصلوا القطار البحري ذاك
Then, are we gonna catch up with them soon?
أسنلحق بهم قريبًا إذًا؟
Probably.
ربما
Alright! We're closing in on our enemy!
!مرحى! اقتربنا من العدو
Yeah!
!أجل
Go, Rocketman!
!انطلق يا روكيت مان
We're gonna beat up that pigeon jerk!
!سنبرح صاحب الحمامة ضربًا